[
    {"items": 10, "created": "08-15-2023", "updated": "08-15-2023"},
    {"question": "Why do we need Jesus to save us?", "answer": "Because we are born dead in our sin.", "reference": "Ephesians 2:1"},

    {"question": "What does that mean?", "answer": "It means that our sin has separated us from God.", "reference": "Romans 3:23"},

    {"question": "What is sin?", "answer": "Sin is disobeying God’s laws: not loving Him, not loving others, stealing, lying, and more.", "reference": "1 John 3:4"},

    {"question": "Why does God get to make laws everyone has to follow?", "answer": "Because He is the Creator, Sustainer, and Sovereign Ruler over all things. His Creation, His rules.", "reference": "Psalm 103:19"},

    {"question": "Can’t we just try to live a good life?", "answer": "You can certainly try, but you’ll never be good enough. God’s standard is perfection.", "reference": "Romans 3:10"},

    {"question": "Then how can we be saved from sin if there’s no hope for us to be good enough?", "answer": "That’s why we need Jesus. Jesus is the Son of God who, before time began, purposed with God the Father to save us because He knew we’d need Him.", "reference": "John 3:16"},

    {"question": "How does Jesus save us?", "answer": "Jesus was born into history, lived a righteous (sinless) life we could never live, and took God’s wrath for sin upon Himself to save people like you and me. He died a physical death and rose again to live forever so that we can live forever with Him.", "reference": "Romans 5:8"},

    {"question": "So Jesus isn’t dead?", "answer": "No! He is alive and is seated at the place of honor at God’s right hand in Heaven. There He advocates for us and prepares a place for us to live with Him forever.", "reference": "1 Corinthians 15:3-4"},

    {"question": "What if I like who I am and what I do even if it is sin?", "answer": "That’s possible. But if what you’ve read here about Jesus makes you have grief and sorrow because of your sin, then that is evidence of the work of God the Holy Spirit changing your heart.", "reference": "Ezekiel 36:26"},

    {"question": "What must I do to be saved?", "answer": "Repent & believe! Turn away from sin and believe in Jesus and what He has done. Leave behind everything and follow Jesus Christ with your whole being.", "reference": "Mark 1:15"}
]